<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on Brute Coding</title>
    <link>https://www.brutecoding.com/tags/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on Brute Coding</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2017. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 19:31:15 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.brutecoding.com/tags/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Load Server Side Data before Bootstrapping your Angular 5 application</title>
      <link>https://www.brutecoding.com/posts/load-server-data-before-init-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 19:31:15 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.brutecoding.com/posts/load-server-data-before-init-app/</guid>
      <description>Ever wanted to load server-side data before loading your application? Or ever wanted to make a HTTP request before having your application bootstrapped. You can do this by injecting HttpClient into main.ts by using the StaticInjector that was introduced in Angular 5. This is what your main.ts file should look like:
function interceptingHandler(backend, interceptors = []) { if (!interceptors) { return backend; } return interceptors.reduceRight((next, interceptor) =&amp;gt; new HttpInterceptorHandler(next, interceptor), backend); } class MyBrowserXHR implements XhrFactory { public build() { return new XMLHttpRequest(); } } class HttpInterceptorHandler { private next; private interceptor; constructor(next, interceptor) { this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Environment for Angular Development</title>
      <link>https://www.brutecoding.com/posts/setting-up-environment-for-angular-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 22:27:54 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.brutecoding.com/posts/setting-up-environment-for-angular-development/</guid>
      <description>Tools you&amp;rsquo;ll be requiring during this process  node.js angular-cli Any text editor (here are some I would recommend):  Visual Studio Code Atom Sublime 3 Notepad++   Installing node.js  I&amp;rsquo;d recommend downloading the LTS build (current build is for devs and might have some bugs in it therefore it might be unstable)   Do not change these options unless you know what you are doing It might impact you to not be able to access node from the cmd if you make some changes here  Installing angular-cli  Start off with closing all your cmd &amp;amp; powershell windows Ensure you have node installed:  Open cmd (by searching from the start menu or by pressing windows + r and typing in cmd) Type node -v followed by npm -v; If you recieve an error on any of the following commands go through the previous step  Install angular-cli by running npm i -g @angular/cli (-g flag enabled the flag for global) Now you&amp;rsquo;re good to go and start creating angular applications  Creating your first Angular application  Open a shell at a location where you want the new application to be installed e.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>